copytrans.net 2019-03-30

# Privacy policy

Loading...

This privacy policy explains how Ursa Minor Ltd (trading as CopyTrans) or ‘we’ use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website and our products.

## What information do we collect about you on our website?

We collect information about the website usage through Google Analytics as soon as you start browsing our website. We also collect information when you make a purchase on our website and voluntarily comment on our posts.

The information we collect with Google Analytics may include your device, location, language, browser, and pages you visited on our website. When you make a purchase on our website we collect basic information required for an invoice: your name, address, and email address.

## What information do we collect about you when you use the software?

When you activate the software we collect basic information about your PC: PC name, IP address, date and time activated. By default, the program will send error logs to our servers. We collect those logs to resolve issues in a timely manner. You can always disable this feature in app Settings. 

## Why do we collect your information?

We collect information about you to process your order e.g. forward you an invoice along with the activation codes, provide customer support and resolve issues and, if you agree, to email you about other products, promotions and information we think may be of interest to you. We may also contact you directly to follow up on the service and user experience we provide. We make sure that we do not collect any personal data from you we do not need. 

## How long do we store your information?

If Ursa Minor Ltd provides any paid services to you we are required under the Tax Law to keep your basic personal information (name and address) for a minimum of 7 years. After that, we still keep the data in order to identify you and provide activation codes. You can request to remove your records, however you will lose the technical possibility to activate the program. We do not provide refunds in such cases. 

## Other services on our website

We use [Google Analytics](https://privacy.google.com/businesses/compliance/#?modal_active=none) and [Yandex.Metrica](https://metrica.yandex.com/about/info/gdpr) to track the perfomance on our website. Comments on our pages are powered by [Disqus](https://blog.disqus.com/protecting-users-privacy-on-disqus). We also use [Reziew](https://www.reziew.com/installation/) – a platform where users can share their experience with our software. Once in a while we send marketing emails through [MailChimp](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/). All the services have their own privacy policy.

## Cookies

Cookies are text files placed on your computer. They contain standard internet log information when you browse our site. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.

## Marketing

We would like to send you promotional offers about products which may be of interest to you. If you don’t want to receive newsletters, you may unsubscribe anytime.

## Accessing your information

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email us at [copytrans@copytrans.net](mailto:copytrans@copytrans.net?subject=I%20have%20a%20question:).

## How to contact us

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you at this email [copytrans@copytrans.net](mailto:copytrans@copytrans.net?subject=I%20have%20a%20question:).

## Updates to our privacy policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on November 14, 2018.
